<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hugo on BLOGS</title>
    <link>https://github.com/PrachiC25/myblog-hugo-/tags/hugo/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hugo on BLOGS</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 09:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/PrachiC25/myblog-hugo-/tags/hugo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Responsive Web Design</title>
      <link>https://github.com/PrachiC25/myblog-hugo-/2024/08/25/introduction-to-responsive-web-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://github.com/PrachiC25/myblog-hugo-/2024/08/25/introduction-to-responsive-web-design/</guid>
      <description>Responsive web design is a critical approach in modern web development. It ensures that your website looks great and functions well on all devices, from desktops to mobile phones.&#xA;What is Responsive Web Design? Responsive web design (RWD) is a design strategy that allows web pages to adapt to different screen sizes and orientations. By using flexible layouts, images, and CSS media queries, a responsive website can provide an optimal viewing experience across a wide range of devices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hugo</title>
      <link>https://github.com/PrachiC25/myblog-hugo-/2024/08/23/hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://github.com/PrachiC25/myblog-hugo-/2024/08/23/hugo/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re new to Hugo, this post will guide you through the initial setup and get you started with your first Hugo site.&#xA;Installation To install Hugo, follow these steps:&#xA;Download Hugo: Go to the Hugo Releases page and download the latest version for your operating system. Install Hugo: Extract the downloaded file and add the Hugo executable to your system PATH. Creating Your First Site Once Hugo is installed, you can create a new site with the following command:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Hugo</title>
      <link>https://github.com/PrachiC25/myblog-hugo-/2024/08/22/understanding-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://github.com/PrachiC25/myblog-hugo-/2024/08/22/understanding-hugo/</guid>
      <description>Hugo is a fast and flexible static site generator that helps you build websites quickly. In this post, we’ll explore its features and benefits.&#xA;Features of Hugo Speed: Hugo generates static files rapidly. Flexibility: Customize your site with themes and templates. Stay tuned for more tips and tutorials on using Hugo effectively.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My First Post</title>
      <link>https://github.com/PrachiC25/myblog-hugo-/2024/08/22/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://github.com/PrachiC25/myblog-hugo-/2024/08/22/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my blog! This is my first post where I’ll introduce you to Hugo and static site generation.&#xA;What is Hugo? Hugo is a powerful static site generator that allows you to build websites quickly and efficiently. It’s known for its speed and flexibility, making it a popular choice among developers for creating blogs, portfolios, and documentation sites.&#xA;Key Features of Hugo Blazing Fast Build Times: Hugo generates static files in seconds, regardless of the size of your site.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
